Draper Corporation Photographs 6612 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Contact prints from glass plate negatives, Series A:1179-1220: box no. 59-60, black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1185: Spoon and potato race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1185. August 1924. Image shows five girls engaged in race; one girl is wearing a hat (she can also be seen in Item 1193). Girl in foreground has just dropped her potato in her box and is starting back to retrieve another. Spectators are scattered on the grass in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1181, Item 1184, Item 1193, and Item 1194, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1186: Girls' race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1186. August 1924. Image shows approximately twelve girls engaged in a race; many spectators are in the background, a couple with umbrellas. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1187: Broad jump, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1187. August 1924. Image shows a young man completing a broad jump; judges squatting on left to better observe length of jump; spectators behind them. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1190 and Item 1191, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1188: Hurdle race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1188. August 1924. Image shows two young men just clearing hurdles; a judge squats on the right to determine clearance; spectators on the left. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1189, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1189: Hurdle race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1189. August 1924. Image shows two young men in the middle of jumping over the hurdles; racer on left has knocked down his hurdle; spectators on left; flagpole in center rear of image. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1188, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1190: Broad jump, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1190. August 1924. Image shows young man at the moment of completing his jump-- his left foot ankle deep in sand. Two judges are squatting to observe his landing; spectators are behind them. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1187 and Item 1191, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1191: Broad jump, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1191. August 1924. Image shows young man at the moment of completing his jump-- both feet ankle deep in sand. Two judges are squatting to observe his landing; spectators are behind them. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1187 and Item 1190, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1192: Pole race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1192. August 1924. Image shows three teams of three boys each racing with a pole between their legs. Spectators in the background; a flagpole is in the center background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1193: Spoon and potato race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1193. August 1924. Image shows four older girls engaged in race; two girls in foreground are approaching their boxes to drop in their potato, one wears a hat (she also appears in Item 1185). Spectators are scattered on the grass in background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1181, Item 1184, Item 1185, and Item 1194, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1194: Girls' potato race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1194. August 1924. Image shows several girls; one is throwing her potato in the box and another is racing back to retrieve another potato. Several male judges are hunched over the boxes. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1181, Item 1184, Item 1185, and Item 1193, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1195: The Norvelles [?], 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1195. August 1924. Image depicts a team of two trapeze artists entertaining crowd of spectators in background and young children sitting on grass in foreground; young woman is on rings and her male partner is standing to left. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1196 and Item 1197, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1196: The Norvelles [?], 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1196. August 1924. Image depicts a team of two trapeze artists (young man and girl) with crowd in background and children sitting on the grass in foreground. The man is swinging from a rope that is hanging from the neck of the woman who is, in turn, hanging upside down above him. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1195 and Item 1197, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1197: The Norvelles [?],Hopedale, Massachusetts, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1197. August 1924. Image depicts a team of two trapeze artists (young man and girl) with crowd in background and children sitting on the grass in foreground. The young woman is holding onto the man with only one hand as she hangs by her legs from a trapeze swing. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1195 and Item 1196, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1198: Men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1198. August 1924. Image depicts three male runners crossing the finish line of a race; another can be partially seen on the right. An official stands behind them. A few spectators are scattered on the grass in the background. Although blurry, the image captures the strain on the runners' faces as they compete. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1199: Boys' race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1199. August 1924. Image shows about twenty boys just starting to race; all in knickers and shirts; some with caps, and one with a suit jacket. Three male judges with hats are observing the start of the race. Some spectators stand on the left and one male in shirtsleeves is on the far right. Flagpole in center background with building in left background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1200, in this folder, which appears to be a different group of boys. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1200: Boys' race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1200. August 1924. Image shows about fourteen boys just starting the race; some in shirts, knickers and caps, others in shorts and singlets. Several judges with hats stand at right; spectators on left; flagpole and house in background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1199, in this folder, which appears to be a different group of boys. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1201: Finish line of men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1201. August 1924. Image shows four men probably at the finish line; one man in shorts and singlet has crossed the line (he has a "D" on his singlet); another is just about to cross the line; two other men bring up the rear. Two judges with caps can be seen on the right; spectators on left; flagpole and house in background. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1202: Start of men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1202. August 1924. Image shows three men just starting to race; all are dressed in shorts and singlet; one wears dark shorts and another a dark singlet. A judge wearing a cap stands to right; spectators on left; flagpole and house in background. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1205 and Item 1206, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1203: Men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1203. August 1924. Image shows two men racing; man in foreground is dressed in shorts and singlet and may be crossing the finish line; man in rear is dressed in dark shorts and singlet. A judge wearing a cap stands on right; spectators are on left; flagpole and house in background. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1204: Finish line of boys' race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1204. August 1924. Image shows young man dressed in white shorts and singlet crossing finish line; another runner in knickers and shirt brings up rear. Two judges in hats at right; hands of spectator on right can be seen clapping; spectators on left; flagpole and house in background. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1205: Start of men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1205. August 1924. Image shows four men starting race; all are dressed in shorts and singlets; one man has handkerchief tied on his head. One judge stands by a pole on right (with stopwatch?); another walks on left with starting gun in hand. Spectators are lined up on left; a flagpole and house are in background. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1202 and Item 1206, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1206: Start of men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1206. August 1924. Image shows four men just staring the race; all are dressed in shorts and singlets except for one wearing dark shorts. Two judges are standing at far right; pole on right. Part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1202 and Item 1205, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1207: Wheelbarrow race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1207. August 1924. Image depicts four teams of two boys each participating in a wheelbarrow race, most likely as part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. One boy in each team takes the position of the "wheelbarrow" by holding a wheel with handles as the front "wheel" while the other boy holds his legs as if they were the wheelbarrow "handles." A crowd of spectators lines the side of the course on the left; a flagpole is in the distance. Closely resembles Item 1179; see also Item 1180, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1208: Start of 1/4 mile men's race, 1924; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1208. August 1925. Image shows four young men just starting to race; all are dressed in shorts and singlets; a pole and the hand of the starter/judge can be seen on the right. Spectators are lined up on the left; a flagpole is in center background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1209, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1209: Finish line of 1/4 mile men's race, Hopedale, Massachusetts, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1209. August 1925. Image shows one racer, dressed in shorts and singlet, crossing finish line on right side of photo; a judge's hand and pole can be seen on right. Spectators are lined up on the left; there is a flagpole and house in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1208, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1210: Start of 1/4 mile boys' race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1210. August 1925. Image shows about fourteen boys just starting to race; some in shirts and pants and others in shorts and singlets. A male judge stands on the right; spectators are lined up on the left with a flagpole and house in background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1211: Boys' quarter mile race: finish line, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1211. August 1925. Image shows young man crossing finish line; he is dressed in shorts and singlet. Three other competitors are behind him, two in knickers and shirt and another in shorts and singlet. Judges stand at finish line; one on right may be holding a stopwatch. Spectators visible mostly on right; flagpole in center background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1212: Start of men's 220-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1212. August 1925. Image shows six men just starting to race; all are dressed in white shorts and singlets except one wearing a dark singlet. Spectators are lined up on left; flagpole and house in background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1213: Finish of men's 220-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1213. August 1925. Image shows three men finishing the 220-yard race: one is crossing the finish line; another has just reached it; a third is behind those two. All are dressed in white shorts and singlets. Spectators are lined up on left; flagpole and house in background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1214: Start of men's 1/2-mile race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1214. August 1925. Image shows two men starting the 1/2-mile race in the foreground; another two men can be partially seen on the far left. All are dressed in white shorts and singlets except for one man in the far left foreground whose clothes appear darker. A judge with a stopwatch in his hand stands on the far right. Spectators are lined up on the left; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1219, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1215: Finish of men's 1/2-mile race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1215. August 1925. Image shows one man crossing the finish line of the 1/2-mile race in the right foreground; another man can be partially seen on the far right. Spectators line the course on the left; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1216: Second heat of men's 100-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1216. August 1925. Image shows three men participating in the second heat of the men's 100-yard race. One in white shorts and singlet has crossed the finish line first; another in dark singlet and white shorts is behind him; a third man in white shorts and singlet is approaching the finish line. Spectators line the course on the left; a judge stands at the far right. A flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1217, in this folder, for the first heat and Item 1218, in this folder, for the 100-yard finish. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1217: First heat of men's 100-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1217. August 1925. Image shows five men participating in the first heat of the men's 100-yard race. Two men have crossed the finish line while a third is just at the finish line, a fourth approaches the finish line, and a fifth brings up the rear. All are dressed in white shorts and singlets. Spectators line the course on the left; a judge can just be seen at the far right. A flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1216, in this folder, for the second heat and Item 1218, in this folder, for the 100-yard finish. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1218: Finish of men's 100-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1218. August 1925. Image shows three men at the finish line of the men's 100-yard race. The man in the center has his arms raised in triumph, but the man partially seen on the left appears to be ahead of him. All three are dressed in white shorts and singlets. Spectators line the course on the left; a judge appears to look on at the far right. A flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1216, in this folder, for the second heat and Item 1217, in this folder, for the first heat of the 100-yard race. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1219: Start of men's 1/2-mile race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1219. August 1925. Image shows a line of male runners at the beginning of the 1/2-mile race. All are dressed in white shorts and singlets except for one man who wears a dark singlet. Spectators are lined up on the left; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See also Item 1214, in this folder. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1220: Finish of men's 1-mile race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1220. August 1925. Image shows one runner as he crosses the finish line of the men's 1-mile race. Spectators are lined up on the left; a judge in shirtsleeves is partially visible on the right. A flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
- Contact prints from glass plate negatives, Series A:1221-1248: box no. 61, black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1221: Start of boys' 200-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1221. August 1925. Image shows approximately two dozen boys starting off the boys' 220-yard race. All are in knickers and shirts; most are wearing caps; one boy has a tie on. Spectators are lined up on the left side of the course; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. The boy on the far right in the dark shirt appears to win the race (see Item 1222, in this folder, in this folder, for the race finish). Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1222: Finish of boys' 200-yard race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1222. August 1925. Image shows one boy in a dark shirt crossing the finish line on the right, while another runner comes up behind him. Judge on the left points to the winner. Spectators are lined up on the left side of the course; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. See Item 1221, in this folder, for the start of the boys' 220-yard race. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1223: Boys' relay race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1223. August 1925. Image shows two boys approaching the finish line of the boys' relay race. Several judges watch from the right, while another judge stands on the finish line at the left. Spectators line the left side of the course; a flagpole and house can be seen in the background. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1224: Spoon and potato race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1224. August 1925. Image shows three women approaching the finish line of the race where containers are in place for the potatoes to be placed. The idea apparently is to fill the container with potatoes. Note a number of potatoes on the ground. Several judges watch from the sideline, while another judge stands close to finish line. Spectators line the course in the background; a house can be seen in the background as well. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1225: Handoff in relay race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Printed in 1974 from glass plate negative no.A1225. August 1925. Image shows a man on the right in shorts and singlet waiting for the handoff baton while two other runners have passed him on the left; a judge in a straw hat stands at the right. Spectators are lined up in the background with a house and flagpole in the distance. Most likely part of a "Field Day" organized by the Draper Corporation for Draper Corporation employees. 25 x 20.25 cm.
  - Item 1226: Girls' Potato Race, 1925; black and white photograph (Box 6, Folder 5)